Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
In this video, let's explore how to explore different APIs using Eclipse.
在这个视频中，让我们来探讨一下如何使用Eclipse来探索不同的API。
So, let's say I would want to find out everything there is to find out about the List interface.
那么，假设我想找出有关 List 接口的所有信息。
How do I do that?
我怎么做呢？
You can type in Control Shift T or Command Shift T and choose the List class. Type in List and you can
你可以输入 Control Shift T 或 Command Shift T 并选择 List 类。键入List，你可以
choose the List class inside Java SE 9.0.1
选择Java SE 9.0.1中的List类。
So, let's make sure I'm using the right one. So,
所以，让我们确保我使用的是正确的那一个。所以。
this is the interface that I would want to choose, Java util. Over here,
这是我想选择的接口，Java util。在这里。
once you go into a class, you can see the entire source code related to that specific class.
一旦你进入一个类，你就可以看到与该特定类有关的全部源代码。
If you'd want to understand what it is all about, you can try and read the description which is present
如果你想了解它的全部内容，你可以试着读一读顶部的描述。
at the top.
在顶部。
Also present is the list of the methods.
此外，还有方法的列表。
You can also type in Control O or Command O. Control O or command O will get you to the list of the methods
你也可以输入Control O或Command O，Control O或Command O会让你进入方法列表。
which are present in here. So,
这里面有哪些方法。所以。
you can see all the individual methods and if you want to look at a specific one, then you can say
你可以看到所有单独的方法，如果你想看一个特定的方法，那么你可以说
okay, I would want to understand the sort method and you can see the syntax of it and also, you can see
好的，我想了解排序方法，你可以看到它的语法，还可以看到
the Java doc related to that.
与此相关的Java文档。
These are long thing and you can read that it's related to a sort.
这些都是很长的东西，你可以读到它与一个排序有关。
So, this is one of the ways,
所以，这也是其中一种方法。
right. So, if you'd want to directly type in something, you can directly type in Java.util.list
对。所以，如果你想直接键入一些东西，你可以直接键入Java.util.list
and go there. The other way is, let's say, I'd want to say List list = new ArrayList( ), right. So,
然后去那里。另一种方法是，比方说，我想说List list = new ArrayList( ) ，对。所以。
let's say, this is the code I am using and I press Control 1 or Command 1 to import the Arraylist
比方说，这是我正在使用的代码，我按下Control 1或Command 1来导入Arraylist
and Control 1 or Command 1 to import the List as well.
和Control 1或Command 1来导入List。
Once you do this, you can do a Control or Command and Click. So, Control or Command and Click. So, press
一旦你这样做了，你就可以做一个Control或Command and Click。所以，控制或命令和点击。所以，按
Control and Click or press Command and Click.
Control and Click或按Command and Click。
It would also take you to the same place.
它也会把你带到同一个地方。
Now I can look at all the documentation behind the ArrayList class as well. So,
现在我也可以看看ArrayList类背后的所有文档了。所以。
this is the way you can explore API in Eclipse.
这是你在Eclipse中探索API的方法。
You can also look at the methods which are present by pressing Control O or Command O. If you want to understand
你也可以通过按 Control O 或 Command O 来查看其中的方法。
the type hierarchy of list, what are the implementation of the list, all that you need to do is say, right
列表的类型层次，列表的实现是什么，你所需要做的就是，在列表上点击右键
click on the List and say Open Type Hierarchy. That shows the entire Type Hierarchy. So, you can see that
点击列表，然后说 "打开类型层次结构"。这就显示了整个类型层次结构。所以，你可以看到
list interface is implemented by AbstractList, ArrayList, CopyOnWriteArrayList, and lot of other
list接口是由AbstractList、ArrayList、CopyOnWriteArrayList和很多其他的东西实现的。
stuff. You can see what are the different elements, methods, which are present in each of these classes
的东西。你可以看到这些类中有哪些不同的元素和方法。
as well.
也是如此。
If you don't really want all the details, but you just want to have a Quick Type Hierarchy, you can say
如果你不是真的想要所有的细节，而只是想拥有一个快速类型层次，你可以说
right click and Quick Type Hierarchy and this would show the high-level overview of the type hierarchy of
你可以说，右键点击快速类型层次，这将显示该特定接口或类的类型层次的高级概述。
that specific interface or the class. In this quick video, we wanted to give you an overview of how to
该特定接口或类的类型层次。在这个快速视频中，我们想让你了解一下如何使用Eclipse探索不同的API。
explore different APIs using Eclipse.
使用Eclipse探索不同的API。
You can also get the same information by going to Google. All that you need to do is, go to Google and
你也可以通过去谷歌获得同样的信息。你所需要做的就是，到Google上并
type in the interface, list interface I would want to find out more about. So, Java list, I would want to
键入接口，列出我想了解的接口。所以，Java列表，我想
find the documentation related to Java 9. So, I put in jdk 9 and typed in Javadoc. Once you
所以，我输入jdk 9，然后输入Javadoc。一旦你
go in here, you can go ahead and explore the different things related to the list interface. You can see
进入这里，你就可以继续探索与列表接口有关的不同东西。你可以看到
which module it is present, in which package it's present in. You can see all these super interfaces, sub
它存在于哪个模块中，它存在于哪个包中。你可以看到所有这些超级接口、子
interfaces, all the implementing classes, and you can see the description, and also overview of the methods,
接口，所有的实现类，你还可以看到描述，以及方法的概述。
and the description of the methods which are present in here. I hope you had an interesting time in this
以及这里存在的方法的描述。我希望你在这个
video. I'll see you in the next one. Until then, bye bye.
视频。我们在下一集再见。在那之前，拜拜了。